[
  {
    "question":
      "It refers to a structured collection of practices that describes the characteristics of effective processes. \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "Software Process Improvement",
      "CMMI",
      "Process Model",
      "Maturity Level"
    ],
    "answer": "Process Model"
  },
  {
    "question":
      "A generic goal in CMMI which refers to a performed process that is planned and executed in accordance with policy. \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "GG2: Institutionalize a managed process",
      "GG3: Institutionalize a defined process",
      "GG5: Institutionalize an optimizing process",
      "GG1: Achieve Specific Goals",
      "GG4: Institutionalize a quantitatively managed process"
    ],
    "answer": "GG2: Institutionalize a managed process"
  },
  {
    "question":
      "A generic goal in CMMI which refers to a performed process is a process that accomplishes the work necessary to satisfy the specific goals of a process area. \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "GG3: Institutionalize a defined process",
      "GG4: Institutionalize a quantitatively managed process",
      "GG1: Achieve Specific Goals",
      "GG2: Institutionalize a managed process",
      "GG5: Institutionalize an optimizing process"
    ],
    "answer": "GG1: Achieve Specific Goals"
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which of the following describes the Stability Myth? \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "We train our staff and we trust them to practice what they learned. We don't have to monitor them.",
      "We defined, documented, and deployed the process. It should be self-driven. Nothing should go wrong. External verification is not necessary.",
      "Our defined, documented, trained, and used process is stable, and will remain effective without changes.",
      "We have a process because we have a set of standard documents that specify the steps of software development.",
      "Our senior management sponsor believes in process improvement. We don’t have to justify our investment and effort in SPI."
    ],
    "answer":
      "Our defined, documented, trained, and used process is stable, and will remain effective without changes."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is CMMI? \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "A Set of Best Practices for Software & Systems Engineering",
      "Methodology",
      "A Guideline for Continuous Improvement",
      "A \"Certification\""
    ],
    "answer": [
      "A Set of Best Practices for Software & Systems Engineering",
      "A Guideline for Continuous Improvement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What CMMI is NOT? \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "A Set of Best Practices for Software & Systems Engineering",
      "Methodology",
      "A Guideline for Continuous Improvement",
      "A \"Certification\""
    ],
    "answer": ["Methodology", "A \"Certification\""]
  },
  {
    "question":
      "What are the activities to performed in implementing SPI. \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "Process publication, training and deployment.",
      "Establish the process, Institutionalize the process, Feedback and Process Improvement.",
      "Process definition and approval, Lessons Learned and Best Practices",
      "Process improvement"
    ],
    "answer":
      "Establish the process, Institutionalize the process, Feedback and Process Improvement."
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which of the following is NOT a Critical Success Factors in SPI? \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "Management and Prioritization of change.",
      "Learning from feedback results.",
      "Alignment with business strategy and goals.",
      "Dedicated resource to manage the implementation and coordination process improvement activities.",
      "Process Improvement implementation."
    ],
    "answer": "Process Improvement implementation."
  },
  {
    "question":
      "A generic goal in CMMI which refers to a managed process that is tailored from the organization’s set of standard processes according to the organization’s tailoring guidelines. \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "GG4: Institutionalize a quantitatively managed process",
      "GG3: Institutionalize a defined process",
      "GG2: Institutionalize a managed process",
      "GG1: Achieve Specific Goals",
      "GG5: Institutionalize an optimizing process"
    ],
    "answer": "GG3: Institutionalize a defined process"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements describes the importance of a process model? \n\n Select one or more:",
    "choices": [
      "It provides a place to start improving.",
      "It provides a way to define what improvement means for an organization.",
      "It provides a common language and a shared vision.",
      "It provides a framework for prioritizing actions."
    ],
    "answer": [
      "It provides a place to start improving.",
      "It provides a way to define what improvement means for an organization.",
      "It provides a common language and a shared vision.",
      "It provides a framework for prioritizing actions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which of the following is a benefit in using the CMMI? \n\n Select one:",
    "choices": [
      "Getting feedback from the practitioners.",
      "Providing improvement information to SEPG.",
      "Guidance for efficient, effective improvement across multiple process disciplines in an organization.",
      "Collection of best practices from different organization."
    ],
    "answer": "Guidance for efficient, effective improvement across multiple process disciplines in an organization."
  }
]
